A Guide to the Harold P. Fabian papers FA071
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Non-Textual Material, 7
  - Miscellaneous Loose Slides (Box 68, Folder 619)
    29 slides - Caribbean Trips, 1960 and 1964. Scenic views, friends, vacation activities. 20 slides - Menor's Ferry Dedication. Images of the ferry crossing the Snake River with 62 people aboard. 8 slides - probably Ferry Ranch.
    57 slides
  - Business Cards from Friends and Acquaintances (Box 69, Folder 620)
  - Letter Opener (Box 69, Folder 621)
  - Broken Lock from the JY Ranch (Box 69, Folder 622)
  - Nail from the "old Sargent cabin" (Box 69, Folder 623)
  - Menor Ferry Dedication Ceremonies, August 20, 1949 (Box 70, Folder 624)
    General note
    Original.
  - Menor Ferry Dedication Ceremonies, August 20, 1949 (Box 70, Folder 625)
  - Menor Ferry Dedication Ceremonies, August 20, 1949 (Box 70, Folder 626)
  - Menor Ferry Dedication Ceremonies, August 20, 1949 (Box 70, Folder 627)
  - Broadcast of Menor Ferry Dedication Ceremonies - Parts 1-7, August 20, 1949 (Box 70, Folder 628)
  - Nan Budge, Cora Barber, Slim Lawrence re: Jackson Hole, Summer 1957 (Box 70, Folder 629)
  - Nan Budge, Cora Barber, Cal Carrington, 1957 (Box 70, Folder 630)
  - Don Miller, Dick Winger, Cal Carrington re: Jackson Hole, Fall 1957 (Box 70, Folder 631)
  - Laurance S. Rockefeller - National Park Conference, September 16, 1957 (Box 70, Folder 632)
  - Rosenkranz, Schwack, Dr. McLeod - Jackson Hole, Wyoming, September 1957 (Box 70, Folder 633)
  - Horace M. Albright re: Jackson Hole Project from Start, September 1957 (Box 70, Folder 634)
  - Tony Grace and Slim Lawrence, June 1958 (Box 70, Folder 635)
  - Cal Carrington, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 636)
  - Cal Carrington, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 637)
  - Cal Carrington, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 638)
  - Cal Carrington, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 639)
  - Elena Hunt at Wilson, Wyoming, September 2, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 640)
  - Senator Joseph Clark on Jackson Hole, July 18, 1964 (Box 70, Folder 641)
  - Harry Clissold, July 1964 (Box 70, Folder 642)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. Oral History - Harold P. Fabian Interview with Mr. Edwin, July 11, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 643)
  - Harold P. Fabian Addressing Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) Girls on Lucas Porch, July 19, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 644)
  - Harold P. Fabian and Murray Burns, August 23, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 645)
  - Harold P. Fabian, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 646)
  - Dick Winger at Salt Lake City, Winter 1967 (Box 70, Folder 647)
  - Stan Boyle, Jackson Hole, July 1968 (Box 70, Folder 648)
  - Mike Yokel Interview, August 1968 (Box 70, Folder 649)
  - Clover Sturlin, "Clover the Killer", June 20, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 650)
  - Rose Leigh Koops, Beaver Dick's Daughter, Jackson Hole, Wyoming, August 1970 (Box 70, Folder 651)
  - Jess and Lillian Wort at Fabian's, August 21, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 652)
    Master tape.
  - Katherine N. Burt, 89th Birthday, September 6, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 653)
  - Slim Lawrence at Fabian's, September 16, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 654)
  - Slim Lawrence at Fabian's, September 16, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 655)
  - Dr. Joseph Edgar Lyon Interview re: JY Ranch, February 13, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 656)
    Original and duplicate.
  - Dr. Joseph Edgar Lyon Interview re: JY Ranch, February 13, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 657)
  - Marty Murie, [August 22, 1973] (Box 70, Folder 658)
  - Rosie Rosenkranz (Box 70, Folder 659)
    No other identification.
- Harold P. Fabian photographs, 1047
  Fabian, Harold P.
  - Teton Companies (Box 23, Folder 279)
  - Snake River Land Company (Box 23, Folder 280)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Menor's Ferry Restoration - 5x7 Prints and Negatives (Box 23, Folder 281)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Menor's Ferry Restoration - 5x7 Prints and Negatives (Box 23, Folder 282)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc - Menor's Ferry Restoration - 5x7 Prints and Negatives - Dedication Aug 20 1949 (Box 23, Folder 283)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc - Menor's Ferry Restoration - Menor Ranch/Ferry (Box 23, Folder 284)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (Box 23, Folder 285)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (Box 23, Folder 286)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (Box 24, Folder 287)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - 1945 Report (Box 24, Folder 288)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Bar BC Ranch (Box 24, Folder 289)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Menor's Ferry Restoration - Photo Album (Box 24, Folder 290)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Menor's Ferry Restoration (Box 24, Folder 291)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Menor's Ferry Restoration (Box 24, Folder 292)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Menor's Ferry Restoration (Box 24, Folder 293)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Menor's Ferry Restoration - Maud Noble's Cabin (Box 24, Folder 294)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Menor's ferry Restoration - Menor Ranch/Ferry (Box 25, Folder 295)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - JY Ranch (Box 25, Folder 296)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Elbo Ranch / Miller's Economic Report (Box 25, Folder 297)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park (Box 25, Folder 298)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Menor's Ferry Restoration (Box 25, Folder 299)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Menor's Ferry Restoration (Box 25, Folder 300)